iimmgg.com 2010-11-21

# Privacy Policy - iimmgg.com

**iimmgg.com** is founded on the principles of helping people host their pictures, images and photos.  
We know that you care about how your personal information is used and shared, and we take your privacy very seriously.  
Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy.

_By visiting and using **iimmgg.com** website, you are accepting the practices outlined in this Privacy Policy._

This Privacy Policy covers treatment of personal information that **iimmgg.com** gathers when you are on the **iimmgg.com** website and when you use **iimmgg.com** services.  
This policy does not apply to the practices of third parties that **iimmgg.com** does not own or control, or to individuals that **iimmgg.com** does not employ or manage.

### Information Collected by iimmgg.com

We only collect personal information that is relevant to the purpose of our website and to control users uploading and sharing unnapropiate content.  
This information allows us to avoid and fight unnapropiate content. We do not process this information in a way that is incompatible with this objective.

We collect the following types of information from our **iimmgg.com** users:

**Information You Provide to Us:**

Registration: In order for you to use **iimmgg.com** services, such as uploading images and keep track of the clicks, galleries and image editing, you must complete a registration form. As part of this registration form, we require select personal information (including your e-mail address).

**Automatic Information:**

We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. **iimmgg.com** and its authorized agents automatically receive and record certain "traffic data" on their server logs from your browser including your IP address and the page you requested. **iimmgg.com** uses this traffic data to help diagnose problems with its servers, analyze trends, administer the website and avoid use of innapropiate content.

### E-mail Communications

**iimmgg.com** is very concerned about your privacy and we will never provide your email address to a third party. 

### Cookies

Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we tranfer to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to set the language that you want to use and to keep sessions while you use our site.  
The "help" portion of the toolbar on the majority of browsers will direct you on how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to command the browser to tell you when you receive a new cookie, or how to fully disable cookies. We recommend that you leave the cookies activated because cookies allow you to use some of our coolest features.  
Some of our business partners, like our advertisers, may use cookies on our website. We have no access to, or control over, these cookies.

### Sharing Your Information

**iimmgg.com** enables people to see and share the content you upload with one another without ever displaying your personal information.  
Rest assured that we neither rent nor sell your personal information to anyone.

Access to personal information is granted only to:

**iimmgg.com** Personnel: **iimmgg.com** personnel and authorized consultants and/or contractors may have access to user information if necessary in the normal course of **iimmgg.com** business.  
Protection of **iimmgg.com** and Others: We may release personal information when we believe in good faith that release is necessary to comply with a law; to enforce or apply our Terms of Use and other policies; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of **iimmgg.com** , our employees, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection.

### Keeping Information Secure

Your **iimmgg.com** account information is protected by a password for your privacy and security.  
Protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer by logging off once you have finished using a shared computer.  
The password used to create your account, will be stored in our database using encryption systems. In case you forget about your password, we will help you to create a new one, since it is impossible to recover when its encrypted. This guarantee that your password will never be seen by other persons.

Only employees who need personal information to perform a specific job (for example, a customer service representative) are granted access to it. All of our employees are kept up to date on our privacy and security practices.

### Ways to Control Display and Use of Your Information

You may request deletion of your **iimmgg.com** account by e-mailing us at webmaster@iimmgg.com.

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

**iimmgg.com** may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time, at its sole discretion. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used. If we make changes to the Privacy Policy, we will notify you by posting an announcement on the **iimmgg.com** website so you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances if any, it is disclosed.

### Conditions of use

If you decide to visit **iimmgg.com** website, your visit and any possible dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of California state law.

### Effective Date of this Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy is effective as of January 15th, 2008 and last updated Aug 27th, 2008.
